Guide to the Robert Ferro Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings about Ferro, 1983-1988; Series III; 9
  - Interviews
    - Rist, Darrell Yates. Interview, publication unidentified, 1984 Mar (Box 10, Folder 233)
    - Saslow, James. Interview in The Advocate, 1983 Nov 10 (Box 10, Folder 234)
    - Unidentified interviewer. Questions and answers, [1988] (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Articles
    - Bergman, David. "Alternative Service: Families in Recent American Gay Fiction," in Kenyon Review, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 236)
    - Clemons, Walter. "Out of the Closet Onto the Shelves," in Newsweek, 1988 Mar 21 (Box 10, Folder 237)
    - Hall, Richard, "20,000 Gay Titles and Still Growing," in Advocate, 1983 Dec 22 (Box 10, Folder 238)
    - Mordden, Ethan. "Stonewall Lit III," in New York Native, 1983 Nov-Dec (Box 10, Folder 239)
- Oversize, 0.25; (1 box)
  - Ferro, Gae: obituary (in Series I), 1979 May 27 (Box 11, Folder 240)
  - Grumley, Michael, memorial service (in Series I), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 241)
  - The Family of Max Desir: publicity and reviews (in Series II), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 242)
  - Second Son: publicity and reviews (in Series II), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 243)
  - Advocate (in Series II), 1981 Feb 7 (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - New York Native (in Series II), 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 245)
  - Philadelphia Gay News (in Series II), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 246)
  - "The Medicine Man," by Ferro and Michael Grumley (in Series II), 1972-1975, undated (Box 11, Folder 247)
  - Hoctel, Patrick. Interview in San Francisco Sentinel and Reed, Paul. Interview in Bay Area Reporter (in Series III), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 248)